http://www.austblister.com/privacy-policy

HomeAbout Us6 Reasons to Use ABSOur Promise to YouService GuaranteeDid You Know?FacilitiesServicesCold Seal PackagingFoil BlisterCarded Blister PackagingBottle FillingSecondary PackagingPromotional SamplingClamshell Blister PackagingShrink WrappingHand AssemblyRepacking & RelabellingLabellingAccreditationTestimonialsContactQuotesCareers
PRIVACY POLICY
This Privacy Policy describes the terms of our commitment to your privacy.PERSONS OR PARTIES COVEREDThis Privacy Policy is intended to cover all visitors to this website, all subscribers to lists or newsletters. Persons who visit or view this website, whether intentionally or unintentionally, whether solicited or unsolicited, are described herein as "Visitors" and are parties to this Privacy Policy. Subscribers to lists or Newsletters are referred to herein as "Subscribers" and are parties to the Privacy Policy. Persons who join an organization or marketing endeavor (e.g. "affiliates") promoted by this website are called "Members" herein and are covered by this Privacy Policy. Finally, anyone who orders, attempts to order, or receives a product sold (recipients) or advertised from this website is called a "Customer" herein and is subject to this Privacy Policy not only by passive acceptance, but by virtue of the Purchase Agreement contract. The website, its agents, owners, operators, and employees are referred to collectively herein as "Website," "Site," and/or "Seller".
VIEWING AND/OR USE AND/OR COMMUNICATION IS CONSTRUED AS ACCEPTANCE OF THE TERMS OF THIS POLICYAcceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy is a portion of the consideration required for your right to visit the website. If you do not accept these terms, you have no right to visit this site and you are fraudulently using this site.
VISITOR EMAIL ENQUIRIESWebsite visitors who wish to communicate with the website do so under two conditions: one, they give their permission for contact by the website; two, they are subject to the general 'SUBMISSION' agreement of this policy. While your email address may or may not be used to solicit you, it is added to the website's general solicitation database.
INFORMATION OBTAINED FROM REFERRING EMAIL OR REFERRING URLSIf you send a friend an email from this site or if you send the URL or one of our web pages to a friend, you must assume that some data is collected about your IP address or your email address and that of your friend. You must assume that referred emails or web pages may appear to come from your email. You must accept full responsibility for referring pages or email to a friend and agree to indemnify this site for any damage, intentional or unintentional that results from said referrals.
INFORMATION OBTAINED FROM ELECTRONIC MEANS AND 'COOKIES'Many websites, including this one, collect information about your computer, your email address, and your IP address. Cookies can be used to electronically gather information about you. Again, it may or may not be personal information, but it is information and by using this site you are expressly giving permission to use 'cookies' and to use the information gathered from their use to benefit you. You also give permission to collect, archive, retrieve, and use any information collected for product design, product offers to you, and general commercial solicitation purposes by this site or joint venture partners, affiliates, and marketing organizations.
HOW INFORMATION MAY BE USEDThe use of information as described below may or may not be how information that is collected is customarily used by this site. While actual use of any information collected may be used quite conservatively, you must assume that it is not. You must assume that information collected is shared with other persons or entities for commercial purposes. While this is uncommon in practice, you must assume that it is as you make your decision whether or not to view or interact with this website. This type of shared information may include your name, address, phone number, email address and buying habits, as well as other information. This information may be used for general commercial solicitation by this website or other persons it is sold to, rented to, or shared with.
DATA SECURITYThis website takes measures to protect its data that contains information related to you. However, as a consideration for viewing this site or interacting with this site in any manner, you waive all claims of any nature against this site concerning the loss, alteration, or misuse of information. You must assume that it is possible for your personal data to be obtained by others, such as "hackers," and used in an inappropriate manner that may cause you harm and that you agree that the site is not responsible for damages to you.
Ph: (02) 9674 0880
Online Enquiry
Location
